Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Episode 82
Gunduz Bey!
Osman Bey.
Come here.
Come here, Gunduz Bey.
I don't want....
...my brothers and alps blood to shed.
You take alps with you...
...and let the cruels destroy Turks!
They are not to blame!
You deceive them with Vizier and Geyhatu.
You have witnessed throughout your life
what my sword did to the cruels.
Now that you are one of the cruels now...
Then...
You shall get to know
the justice of my sword.
Come on, Gunduz Bey.
Since you consider me an enemy...
Then, I won't back down either, brother.
After all the betrayals you've done...
After all that injustice,
do you still call me "brother"?
Which brothers?
From now on I'm not your brother!
I wouldn't end my brother!
Because of the betrayals you committed....
Your blood is halal to me!
You are a son who betrayed his ancestors.
You are an older brother who left
his younger brother among traitors!
You are a Bey who
has turned his back on his country
You will leave this world without a brother...
a tradition...
and a homeland!
Come here.
"Two days ago"
You really want to kill me, don't you,
Osman Bey?
I can tell it from my own experiences.
Believe me.
There is nothing on this earth
more beautiful than your disappearance.
For the great enemy...
We will ally.
Alliance?
I don't need to ally with anyone.
I am Aya Nikola.
Because the sun is behind you,
you think your shadow is too big
If you don't need anyone...
Why do gather the Lords?
How do you know this?
So, it's not just me.
Geyhatu knows it too.
And he knows that you're
spinning games behind him!
For this reason,
he sent his soldiers to behead you.
Not only you,
but if all the Lords gathered...
You can't do anything in front of the 20,000
Mongol soldiers Arghun Khan sent to Geyhatu.
...20
20,000?
Follow me.
Argun Khan's soldiers are coming.
They will put down the rebellion
of the Turks.
Argun Khan is going straight east.
His army will be under my command.
I will destroy Argun Khan.
His throne will be mine.
And the Seljuk state will also
be within my palm!
Sultan Mesut is at the door of death.
But even when he is like this,
he is still a strong man
You underestimate him too much.
He will do everything to stop you.
I am greater than death, Alam Shah.
Mesut can't do anything.
His youngest son will become the sultan.
And you will become his viceroy(yabgu).
The judgment will be yours
But first...
Nikola.
Nicola won't be able to
achieve what he hopes.
If Nikola had gathered the Lords for war
in order to fulfill his hopes...
This will make us lose time.
Our time is precious, Alam Shah.
Didn't you kill Nikola?
Talk!
I was going to bring Nikola's head to you.
But...
Osman showed up.
Nikola was supposed to die!
What was Osman doing there?
Mingiyan!
Gunduz Bey has come.
Let him!
Get out!
20,000 soldiers are on their way.
No one will be able to stop us.
We'll conquer Inegol first.
Then we will put down the rebellion in
Turkish lands.
20,000?
This will be a massacre.
The end of the rebels must
be a massacre, Gündüz.
You will see and take a lesson out of it.
You will come with your alps,
as you promised, Gündüz
You will fight on our side.
Now the Mongols will attack
us like a torrent!
It's such a torrent that...
it will ruin every nation!
He's knocking on our door now.
He knocked on your door, Osman Bey.
If he ends me, he will come for you soon.
Turks, Romans...
ّSeljuqs...
Rome.
We are all People of the Book.
We must unite against these oppressors.
Osman Bey, Osman Bey!
You're smart and brave, okay.
But you don't even have a throne!
You are telling me about
confronting 20,000 Mongol soldiers!
I am the Bey, son of the Bey.
I don't need to prove my Beyship.
However...
If you don't listen to what I say...
You won't even have a castle to
put your head in...
These lands and Ingol...
It's all mine.
Neither you nor Geyhatu
can take it from me.
Mongols won't take it from you.
Rather, they destroy and crush.
Samarkand, Baghdad.
Bukhara.
Merv.
And many more.
Were they weaker than Ingeol?
Take a lesson out of this.
...not just Inegol...
If we do not unite against the cruels...
The end of Constantinople
will also be the same.
Why did I gather all the Lords?
For war.
I don't need you to defeat Geyhatu.
I don't have any warrior who hasn't fought
Mongols before.
I know strength and weakness of Mongols
very well.
Oghuz's archers are needed
against Mongol's cavalry!
We'll unite so we don't miss our
chance to kill each other.
Is that it?
Okay Osman Bey.
Let's say I agreed.
Let's assume that.
What do you want from me?
You will take me to
Emperor Andronikos.
Osman Bey.
You are the one who said Geyhatu knocks
on our door with 20,000 of his soldiers
These lands will be lost
until we return from Constantinople!
It is not us, but the emperor
will come to us.
How?
The Emperor is coming to Iznik.
And you and I will go to him.
Let everything aside...
How do you know about this?
We certainly know the broken branches
of great trees...
and the future of underripe fruits.
So...
This is our secret :)
Will you also include the Emperor
in the alliance?
I'll make a non-aggression pact
with the emperor.
The ones who leave a mountain behind do not
lose time by checking their back.
Cengiz Khan had conquered the west
before he went for China.
How nice.
Do you take the men we are fighting
as an example for yourself, Osman Bey?
No.
I take minds as guide.
I don't see if wisdom comes
from a friend or an enemy.
Now...
You will come with me to Iznik.
I'll explain this to your emperor too.
He will know as well...
That if the East falls, the West will also fall.
As long as there will be an agreement,
I mean, if it is done...
I will have some conditions too.
Think about your conditions.
Tell me about them before night.
Alps! Let's go.
20,000 soldiers?
Konur, my lion Konur,
Thank Allah you are alive.
I will not die before I make him pay for
what he did to you, Vizier.
You are wounded, did Osman do this?
Go to the infirmary quickly.
We'll talk about what needs
to be done later.
Your order, Vizier.
Celali, notify the commanders.
They shall prepare.
When Geyhatu commands,
we will unite with the alps of Gunduz.
And we march to the rebellious tribes.
Right away, Hadrat Vizier.
-Peace be upon you
-Peace be upon you, Osman Bey.
-Where are you headed?
-To the red apple
- What's the point?
- Shahada!
- For what?
- For homeland.
- Where is homeland?
- The whole world.
The world shall become your home.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Soldiers of Arghun Khan
are about to enter our lands
Have you made your preparations?
Did you get the Lords on your side?
We are always on the alert
As I told you, all the Lords
are on my side.
These lands will become a tomb
for Arghun Khan's soldiers!
What about the rebellious tribes?
Let's say you have exhausted the
vanguard units
What about the rest?
Those who rebel will stand with us.
We will fuel the fire of disobedience with them!
We will encourage those who cannot raise their
heads and see the strength in themselves.
If we burn, we burn together, and if rise,
we rise together.
One of the units of the vanguard of Mongols
has set out on the way.
They are coming from the direction
of Turna valley.
Eyvallah (thank you).
May your path be open, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
What are you saying my daughter?
Yes, mother Selcan, I am pregnant.
Yes mother,
you will have another grandchild!
May Allah forgive your
baby's parents, Mari.
Turgut Bey will be very pleased.
May his/her life be long and blessings
be wide, Inshallah.
Praise be to my pretty daughter.
Can I come in?
Come, Boran.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you
Praise be, mother!
You are standing on your feet!
Thank Allah very much, my son.
My daughter Mari
gave me such news that...
...I can cross the whole tribe
without a break, I swear to Allah
Where are you coming from?
From Osman Bey.
Tell Osman quickly.
Tell him to send Turgut Bey back
to the tribe.
My daughter Mari
has good news to tell him.
Your order, mother.
And Osman Bey has also sent news.
My Beys says that this Julia
never stops chasing after us
Now is the time for revenge.
It's time, Boran.
My Gonca, Alps, and she
shed my mother's blood.
Every breath she breathes
is a shame on us.
Osman Bey says it too.
This bloodless can't stop
watching the tribe.
She will attack at the first opportunity
He told us to get into action
before her and cut her breath.
It's the Bey's command,
Killing her is an obligation now.
Osman Bey knows everything,
even though he is away from his tribe.
The hand of Osman Bey
is always above his tribe, my daughter.
This is what a Bey looks like.
Allah bless my valiant.
Now listen to me carefully.
Now that we are united...
You need training.
Praise be!
Kumral!
I've never missed you, you know?
I entered the cave and did not
stop beating swords.
My hands are tired, but
my head has rested.
Good, never miss me.
I have a new brother for myself.
Yes.
We are in our brother's place...
But who is he and what does he do?
It's you and me at the same time.
The snake does not
abandon its nature, Kosses.
I trust a man I don't know
more than Nicola.
And I'm the one who knows Nikola the best.
I know when, where, and how he will
stab us in the back.
He is totally a snake!
But we must not forget...
...that there are eagle claws
on top of that snake.
Eyvallah.
We'll talk about these subjects in detail
when Osman Bey comes.
Of course.
He didn't say where he went,
but he'll come eventually.
Osman Bey is coming!
Come, there are important topics
that I will tell you about.
Osman Bey.
If you'll excuse me,
I also have something to tell you
Come here
My Bey, it's the merchant taxes in Sogut.
Well done Erdogdu.
But it doesn't belong here.
See if there are any needy people
in the tribe and Sogut.
And distribute the rest to the Ahis.
And tell Alps to always be on alert.
Excuse me, my Bey...
While the Kayi and other tribes
are having hard times,
what's the point of distributing
money to other tribes?
What the Kayi tribe needs most in
this time is praying.
The prayer of the needy is
more valuable than all money
In addition, Ahis use their
shares in trading.
They benefit Sogut.
As the Bey of Kayi,
I say this is appropriate.
The command is Gunduz Bey's.
Erdogdu, don't forget what I said.
Your command, my Bey.
My Gunduz?
Why didn't you take the Kayi taxes?
So that they don't ask for it too.
Vizier Alam Shah.
United with ignoble Geyhatu.
They will attack the rebellious
Turkmen tribes
He asks for my valiant alps.
What are you saying, Gunduz?
There is no turning back of this.
How am I going to get out of this?
I heard Vizier.
They will take over
all the castles, up to Iznik.
And there's more.
Gunduz Bey will give alps and horses
to Geyhatu...
...in order to stop the rebellion in
Turkmen tribes.
And Gunduz Bey will rule the castles
in the name of them.
Gunduz Bey.
The betrayal you committed is beyond Kayi.
It reached all the Turks!
Do you know...
...why Geyhatu does this?
Why does he want Kayi alps...
despite of the arrival of 20,000 Mongol
soldiers sent by Arghun Khan?
His intention is to...
To show that the Kayi and the cruels
are alike.
To killing the seeds of the state that we
will establish before they green!
Who will believe the one who works with
the cruels?
Who will trust their promises?
These Mongol soldiers will
not enter Sogut.
Even if they reach our lands,
they will not get out of here alive
Listen carefully to what I have to say.
The soldiers of the Lords will be
on a wing...
Turgut Bey, you will be with your alps
on the other wing.
Listen to me carefully.
They will never pass from here.
Never.
We will be martyred, Osman Bey.
Since I stood by you, Osman Bey.
I abandoned my loved ones and
my life.
The only truth now...
...is martyrdom for the country.
I don't have a castle anymore
I don't know how loyal
my people to me now.
But I am loyal enough to die for them.
We will stop them, Osman Bey.
Together.
Being together...
Boosts my confidence.
Eyvallah.
But Nikola...
I don't trust him.
What if he doesn't send his soldiers?
What if he leaves us?
We will be deficient, Osman Bey.
He'll send.
My Bey, Rogatus is here.
Let him come.
They did not allow me to enter Nikea.
They didn't consider me a Lord.
They said I don't have a castle.
I know.
Then why did you send me if you knew?
I wanted you to go and
see with your own eyes.
That you can't do anything without me.
I will give you back your Lordship,
your castle, and your soldiers.
I wanted to make sure of your sincerity.
My sincerity
didn't need this, Osman Bey.
Go to Nicola now.
He will tell you something important.
Turahan Alp will join you too.
He will tell you what to do.
Turgut, you go as well.
Not with them, go to the tribe.
There's some important news
that Mari will tell you about.
Be careful.
Sogut.
Nobody knows you came here except for
your Bey, right?
I hid myself even from the birds
on my way here.
You should hide from them more
at this time.
The situation is not good.
We departed on this road in order to break
the unfornute, Vizier Alam Shah
There will certainly be difficulties.
It's not difficulty.
If we can't pervent it in time...
It will be our end.
20,000 Mongol soldiers who are
coming to Geyhatu...
...will raid your Bey...
...after they complete their work here.
That they reach there means
the end for all of us.
We'll stop them in time then.
What do you think to do, Vizier Alam Shah?
I will set Geyhatu up in a way that
he has never seen in his life.
His filthy soldiers wil
l never trample our lands.
My Bey's confidence in you is infinite,
Vizier Alam Shah, may Allah help you.
Eyvallah.
Inegol Castle.
It means that Samuel has been
with Kosses since the beginning.
Well, how could you not see this, Argos?
No, no!
They took my sword at the door.
You can calm down.
What are you doing here?
So, it means that the situation
is very dangerous.
- So Osman deceived us all.
- No.
Osman does not deceive anyone.
You're on the right side, be sure of this.
Osman Bey asked me to inform you.
Geyhatu, Vizier Alam Shah and Gunduz Bey.
They intend to take over all
the castles including Inegol Castle
After they have taken
over the castles of all the Lords...
They will leave the Mongol soldiers in the
borders of Inegol and attack Karamanogullari.
Osman Bey has birds everywhere.
He knows everything right away.
My Bey knows every breath the infidels
breathe, from your lands to Mount Tengri.
We are grateful.
You can get out.
I want you to stay here tonight, Rogatus.
You'll take my soldiers
to Kosses and Turgut in the morning.
Turgut is the commander of
this strange army.
You will also carry out his commands.
Literally.
What does this mean?
I will not serve under a
Turkish commander!
I thought you were very happy to
have Osman next to you, Rogatus.
He wanted this.
You will abide by.
That means
we'll put up with Turgut until this is over.
My Mari.
Turgut.
I miss you from the heart.
Me too.
Osman Bey said that you were waiting for me
and you were to tell me something.
Are you fine?
Turgut.
From now on, your eyes will not only
shine like a star when you look at me .
but also when you look at her/him.
I'm pregnant
We will have a child, Turgut
A child?
...You are....
Did you say a child?
how?
...We are now
...I
Will I be a father?
Yes
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah, Mary, thank Allah.
Thank Allah
You will be a father, Turgut Bey!
I will be a father.
I'm going to be a father.
But I...
How will I protect you now?
The Mongols are coming.
I will not entrust you to Gunduz who
handed you over...
to Vizier at the first opportunity.
I'll take you to a safe place
...we'll be separated for a while, but...
Understand me.
If something happens to you...
I will burn myself and
this world with me, Mary
Understand me.
If you will come eventually...
I will always wait for you, Turgut.
I will definitely come.
My mind and heart will always be with you
Come on, get ready.
Let's get out of here quickly.
Okay.
Let's og.
Is that your number?
There is no shortage.
We are complete.
Are you going out like this
in front of our emperor?
We're going to talk.
No need for a large number of people
to speak.
We have what we need.
Excuse my curiosity, Osman Bey.
How do you know that the emperor
will trust you and won't kill you?
Today, the emperor will decide whether
Constantinople will be...
...Turks' or Mongols'.
Osman.
I will kill your loved ones one by one.
And then you.
Malhun.
So, it's your turn.
You will die today.
Come on, we'll follow them.
Today there is a cannibal in my share.
The bird, the bird!
You're hungry, cannibal, aren't you?
You are hungry
Eat it!
Won't you eat?
Okay.
As you like.
You shouldn't have touched the bird.
Welcome.
I brought your army to be at your command.
Turgut Bey.
Eyvallah (thank you)
Don't do this my old friend.
You are still a religious man.
Protecting our people is
your primary mission.
And Turgut Bey will help
us succeed in this.
I don't say this because he is my family.
Do not worry
He's a good leader.
And a brave soldier.
I only protect my citizens.
However, since
the majority made such a decision...
I am at your command, Turgut Bey.
I'm honored, Rogatus.
Your standing with us will
make us stronger.
Since you are with us...
Eyvallah (thank you).
So...
What do we do now?
Shall we attack without wasting time?
The attack has already started.
The game I set up is currently
running without any problems.
The situation is bad, my Bey.
Geyhatu is coming with his soldiers.
And Vizier is with im.
They are very crowded.
Geyhatu.
For the sons and daughters of Erlik Khan.
Welcome, Geyhatu.
The best commander of Argun Khan.
That's for sure.
For the sons and daughters of Erlik Khan.
We've brought the Greek fire,
we'll burn the walls.
The castles of the Lords will become ours.
The war will begin.
There will be a lot of blood.
A lot of blood for Erlik Khan.
Damn it.
We can't attack while Geyhatu is there.
It will be our end.
But we must find a way.
Osman Bey trusts me.
I'd rather this to be my last war than
not keep the promise I made to him.
And let my death be at
the hands Mongols.
Also, while Cerkutay is there...
...we cannot go back because
Geyhatu has come
Do not order us to retreat, Turgut Bey.
We can die but we cannot retreat.
Don't worry, Turahan.
You'll get used to it, my old friend.
Look at me, do I ever get surprised?
It's Konur, Alps.
I will help you.
How?
Sogut.
Now that we are in the bazaar...
We should buy whatever you need, Aygül.
As you know, the return of my Osman Bey
is soon.
You take care of me with all your worries.
Thank you, Malhun.
My mother is determined. We'll have
your wedding once they return.
Inshallah, they will come back safely.
Come.
- Demonstrate that one, will you?
- Of course
This color here is more vivid.
This color suits you so much.
What is going on here?
Let's see that one too.
Boran!
Take these.
Eyvallah (okay).
Come on, brothers.
Let's go.
Sir, Konur arrived.
No one was to know that
we would be here, Vizier.
There is clearly something important.
Let him come.
Is everything okay, Konur?
I told you to stay in the inn.
Why did you come?
I wouldn't have come if it wasn't
important, Vizier.
Osman.
I've been following him
since the night.
I found the place they stay.
But they are crowded.
I couldn't attack them.
How crowded could they be?
They are helpless against the
Mongol soldiers!
Soldiers! Move!
My Bey!
My Bey, Konor Alp, took Geyhatu and Vizier
out among the soldiers.
Thank him.
Now, it's time to act.
Get everyone ready
We will attack!
No mercy on Mongols!
If necessary, we will die!
Around Iznik Castle.
Let's rest a bit here.
This place is better for resting.
Take this.
All exits and entrances to the castle
were drawn here.
Examine which road is better and
which way is safer.
Confirm the accuracy of the entrances and
exits of the castle.
If not, draw a new one.
My Bey.
You saw my tent.
Oh, what a shepherd you are!
Do you think you're the only one
who knows how to hide?
My Bey.
I was waiting for the right
time to tell you
But I've been exposed.
We ask you your name...
All you say is " I am shepherd."
Tell me.
My mother named me Akca.
and put faith in my heart.
My father taught me to ride a horse.
And taught me how to use a sword.
I was a shepherd who had a herd.
One day, Lord's dogs
raided my herd, my Bey.
My father
My father, my Bey...
My father was martyred,
and I was captured.
They gave me to an Armenian carpenter,
and he educated me.
But I am Turkish, Osman Bey.
I will not be captivated.
My heart is always free.
I painted every detail in order to escape.
There is not a single stone that
I do not know.
I said...
One day I will attack these walls...
I swore.
My Bey, I've been waiting for you to
make this moment real.
And one day you came as a wounded Turk
and entered in the midst of my herd!
Thank Allah, my Bey.
When the path we walk is one...
It was always possible
that we would meet, Akca.
Right people will be on the right path.
Do they...
...do they know, my Bey?
My Bey...
Ignore my sanity, or insanity.
It is difficult sometimes.
No.
You don't control your mind.
So that we conquer all the castles!
Eyvallah, my Bey.
I will be by your side all the life
that my Creator gives me
Osman Bey.
The emperor protects
his castle with the best soldiers.
Do you think they will let the
brave, rebel...
...yet a former Bey of Kayi?
Until I die...
...I am the Bey of Kayı, Nikola.
You will see.
I will get dangerously close to
the Emperor.
So, all those soldiers in the castle will
let you in without a doubt.
Is that so?
Why do you think I brought you with me?
What is it in your mind?
You will introduce me as a spy you sent
among the Turks.
No one will know who I am...
...until we meet the Emperor.
Osman Bey!
For Erlik Khan's sons and daughters!
Cannibal dogs!
Governor Saguros is not available.
I came to meet the Emperor,
not Governor Saguros.
Nikola!
Eldoris!
The closest to the Emperor...
...Eldoris!
What are you doing here?
Let's say I want to be close to
the Emperor like you.
Emperor Andronikos is here but no one
knows.
You are accessing information that doesn't
concern you.
We came here with crucial information,
Eldoris.
Can you inform the Emperor?
Please.
Who is this?
He is a spy I put among the Turks much
time ago.
He also knows information that doesn't
concern him.
He wants to share them only with
the Emperor.
No!
Only you, Nikola.
Even the reason he is here is me.
I will only tell it to the Emperor.
Even Nikola doesn't know.
So he is an important enough spy to
call you by your name.
Really...
...who are you?
I'm the one who will save your castles
from falling to Mongolian.
Eldoris...
...the Emperor.
Mighty Emperor Andronikos...
...I know you don't want to get
interrupted while working but...
Cut it short, Eldoris.
Speak.
The Lord of İnegöl, Aya Nikola wants
to see you.
We have a huge information gap.
Let him in.
He is with an unknown Turk.
He said that he is a spy.
An unknown Turk?
Honorable Emperor...
...as if it wasn't enough for me to
be under the same sky as you...
...now I'm here before you.
I am honored.
And I greet you with respect.
How did you know I'm here, Nikola?
I told him.
Who are you?
Osman Bey, son of Ertugrul Gazi.
Osman!
Don't, Osman!
Don't!
Open the door!
Don't you dare make a mistake!
Idiot Nikola!
How can you get a Turk into my room!
Open the door!
Emperor!
If my intention was to fight...
...there would be ten thousand horsemen
behind these walls.
I just want to talk...
...Emperor.
Just to talk.
Let him go.
Come on!
Hurry!
What happened here?
Catch the horse!
So, we will perish if we are not united
against the Mongols.
I don't live in a tent, Osman.
I have walls.
I have waters guarded by a giant chain.
When the day comes, all can be
dealt with, Your Imperial Highness.
But let's say...
...it keeps you safe for now.
So how will you feed Constantinople...
...when there is a massacre in the east?
Your wheat is enough for you
only eight months.
More than half of gutters need repairs.
What about the army?
It's not enough to quell a civil war.
None of these things are a reason
for me to ally with you.
Right..
You are right.
When the time comes, you make your
alliance with the Catholic Latins.
They will save Constantinople.
Or ask the Pope for a crusader army.
Behave, Osman!
It's not your place to talk about
my co-religionists.
Moreover, the Mongols have not yet
reached my walls to besiege my city.
You Muslims besieged the city
every chance you got.
Maybe...
...I should write a letter to
Argun Khan...
...we should corner you between us
and destroy you.
Your Imperial Highness...
...we Muslims make a home from the lands
we conquer.
We restore the places we conquer.
What about the Mongols?
When they come, they destroy the land
and kill everyone.
Is it up to you to think about
the future of Constantinople?
I take the troubles of all innocents
to myself, Your Imperial Highness.
But...
...if we don't stand together...
...they will destroy all of us one by one.
The Vanguard comes before...
...the Army of twenty thousand.
I would like to make a deal...
...before facing them.
I want to secure my back as I fight...
...to the last drop of my blood.
Therefore...
...I want the castles taken from Rogatus
and Kosses to be given back.
I want to graze my animals freely
in your pastures.
And...
...I want Nikola's loyalty.
Since he got you all the way
into my room...
...Nikola is already loyal to you.
I want the other Lords at far away to
be under my command too.
What if you can't succeed after having
such a great power, Osman Bey?
Then you also will have destroyed
my strength of resistance.
Everything has a point when you have
a cause.
We fight for neither name nor glory.
The only thing that matters to us
is the safety of people.
If they pass us...
...they won't even have the power to
come to you.
You also will be rid of a Turk Bey.
You will be winning, either way, Emperor.
You will win.
How did this happen?
Choke it!
Red Shaman.
Trap!
Protect the chests!
Come on!
Your end is near, cannibal.
Traitor!
Choke it! Choke it!
All right, I'll do that.
No!
Blood! Blood! Blood!
It will be night soon.
What if she changed her
mind?
She will deal with it today.
Obviously, attacking in the crowd
didn't work for her.
She is not brave enough to face us.
She can only go behind our backs.
Vile dog!
They are too crowded, we can't get close.
Malhun will die today!
Something is happening.
You wait here.
Come on.
Malhun is leaving, alone.
Go after her, now!
Good job, brother Cerkutay.
You are such a valiant.
Congratulations, Cerkutay.
Now I understand better why
Osman Bey trusted you his eyes closed.
Thank you.
They brought chests of fire, Turgut Bey.
They were going to break the walls
with these.
They would destroy many castles.
They protected them with their lives.
They lost their lives.
Now, we have the fire.
Both the power and the danger are in
our palms.
Geyhatu's wrinkled face will get
even more wrinkled...
...when he hears this news.
Get ready at once, Alps!
We will go to Osman Bey and tell him
we got the fire.
My Osman Bey will be the happiest
about this.
Come on!
My Bey...
...I say we first hit İznik if they don't
accept the deal.
They will accept it.
I made sure they know what will happen
if they don't.
Osman Bey.
I was so sure the Emperor were going to
kill you.
You were so sure that you would kill me
too.
The Emperor trusts you.
It's a sign of his trust.
Until we banish Geyhatu from
these lands...
...every Lord under my command will be
by your side, Osman Bey.
Emperor Andronikos.
I will be waiting to hear from you,
Osman Bey.
Goodbye, for now.
Be careful.
The big battle is near.
Soldiers!
They have just moved.
Clearly, his watchmen saw us coming.
They went this way.
The tracks are fresh.
Spread around!
Search everywhere!
Find Osman and follow him!
Come on!
-Malhun!
-Julia!
You dog!
Welcome to your death, Malhun!
You can handle me only when I am
alone, right?
Why didn't you attack me at Söğüt?
I don't like hard work.
Now, you will die.
You're wrong, Julia, It's not me who will
die today, it's you.
But when you have the blood of many
innocent people in your hands...
...your death won't be easy.
Die!
Boran!
I came here to kill you, you dog!
You will die today!
-Trap!
-Come on, Alps!
How did you catch me, Malhun?
It wasn't hard at all, Julia.
At all.
Come on, kill me!
Kill me!
You will die but, you will die slowly!
Praise be!
For those you killed!
Allahu Akbar!
Boran, stop!
Boran, I said stop!
-Calm down!
-Boran!
Boran!
Be patient!
Listen to me!
Söğüt
Even if we didn't get results, your effort
is admirable, Konur.
I am honored, my Vizier.
Can I come in, my Vizier?
Come in.
My Vizier, Nikola sent news with his man.
He will visit Geyhatu.
He wishes you to join them.
So, he is still alive.
And he wants me to join, is that so?
Nikola!
If he wants that much I will join them.
I will be there when Geyhatu tears
his filthy head from his body.
Murderer!
Murderer! Murderer! Killer
Killer! Murderer!
Dog! Killer! Murderer!
Murderer!
You filthy infidel!
You killed Gonca!
You deserve to die!
Killer! Murderer!
Killer! Murderer! Kill her!
Infidel!
You deserve to die, you killer!
Killer! Murderer!
I will kill all of you!
Filthy Turks!
Killer! Murderer!
Kill her!
-Murderer! Traitor!
-You will die!
You deserve it!
Murderer! Murderer!
Die!
You deserve to die! Killer!
Murderer!
Get up!
Murderer! You will die!
You deserve to die!
You will be punished, Julia!
The mothers of the people you killed
without blinking deserve vengeance!
Now you will pay for Gonca and
my mother.
You separated those innocent children from
their mothers.
You tortured them in many ways. Did you
think you could get away with it?
I am going to kill you!
Shut up!
What is going on here, Malhun Hatun?
While you sit on your throne, we catch
traitors, Gündüz Bey!
Good job.
This devil lived longer than necessary.
How did you do it?
Osman Bey, the Bey of Kayı, ordered.
My Bey is still watching us even when he
is not here.
He predicts all kinds of trouble
and takes precautions
Even like this, Osman Bey took our
revenge.
Osman Bey! Osman Bey! Osman Bey!
Long live Osman Bey! Long live Osman Bey!
Thank you, Hatuns!
Praise be!
I would leave you to these mothers but...
Alps!
Take her to the lattice tent!
Inegöl Castle
Rogatus!
I guess Osman's plan worked.
You look like you won.
We must include Turks and Mongols
in our armies.
They come in handy when needed.
We won, Nikola.
Osman Bey was right.
You don't need fire to attack
the tribes.
You need it only if you want to attack
the Lord Castles.
They were going to break our walls
with fire, is that so?
Now I am definitely sure that I am on
the right side.
Where is the fire?
Osman has it.
What do you say, Rogatus?
Is this a lesser threat?
Calm down, Nikola.
You are now sure that you are on
the right side.
Emperor Andronikos ordered us to support
Osman.
I will go to Geyhatu and convince him...
...that I am still on his side.
The game must continue.
Praise be!
My valiants!
You destroyed those dogs!
We didn't leave a single one alive,
my Bey.
Great! Thank you.
Kosses, thank you too.
You also helped.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Fighting for our loved ones with you...
...is an honor.
But to be honest...
...actually Konur saved us from this tough
situation.
Thank you.
What about the fire?
Did you bring it?
Of course, we did, my Bey.
It is with Master Davut.
So, Geyhatu wanted to take the castles
this way.
Yes, my Bey.
I heard those cannibals talking.
They were going to break the walls
with it.
Geyhatu, you will grumble in the gizzard.
I will burn you with that fire.
Look who is here?
Bala!
And the old woman!
Why didn't you die!
I will kill all of you one by one when
I get out of here!
You vile dog!
You can't hurt anyone any more!
You killed my Gonca, killed the alps!
You even tried to kill children!
I should've killed the children
right away!
We would have gotten rid of
a few filthy little Turks.
Oh, my girl. Who raised you like this,
without love.
You are talking about killing innocent
children.
I pity you, my girl.
I pity you.
Shut up, old woman!
Why are you still alive?
Shut up!
Snake!
You are right, I should've died.
But I survived with the love of my
children.
I am here because of their prayers.
You can't understand this.
You were never loved.
You always lived with hatred and grudge.
But you weren't born like this.
Oh, my girl.
One has both good and evil within
herself.
You always fed the evil side of yours.
Your goodness faded away.
Your beauty, your youth...
All turned into a desert.
You don't know anything, old woman!
Shut up!
I am going to kill you!
Then you!
Then that monster in your belly!
You!
Bala, enough.
Come on, my girl.
You will die first, you devil!
You'll die!
We will all die one day.
We're not afraid of death.
However, you better start praying.
Pray, so that Allah accepts it.
You will die!
I'll kill you all!
Come here!
Bala! Come here!
Gündüz Bey sent this for the Ahis.
The Ahis took it from those who
were in heedlessness...
and gave it to those who are
on the right path.
We...
said that it is the right of our Osman
Bey, so we brought it to you.
Thank you, my Sheikh.
Thank you.
Thank Ahis for me.
These difficult days will pass.
Your valiants are increasing
from day to day.
However, the state is a bird.
It needs two wings, Osman Bey.
You have many valiants, you
have many men.
What about scholars?
Even in this situation, my Sheikh?
Osman Bey, you live in a shepherd's tent.
You don't give up on the state.
Master Davud works actively
with the blacksmiths.
So many heroes support him.
He who waits for his time
is always late, Osman Bey.
The time is now.
You are right, my Sheikh.
What would you
like to do?
With your permission, I would like to
send messengers to all lands.
I also want the doctrinal foundations for
the blessed state that you will establish.
And may the bottom of your
flag be filled with scholars.
My son-in-law, Dursun Fakih, is on the
road with my daughter.
That's so good, my Sheikh.
Which permission? They are welcomed.
Let us host them.
They always have a place in our hearts.
Tell me, Osman Bey.
What is on your mind?
My Sheikh.
I need your permission.
My brother...
stabbed me in the back.
He deceived many Turkmens.
My Sheikh.
Is my brother's blood halal for me?
Wait.
Wait for me, Bala.
Open the door, brother.
Boran.
You will die first.
You don't talk.
Have you lost your toxic tongue?
Mad Boran.
I wasn't waiting for you.
You loved your wife like crazy, right?
Shut up, demon.
I'll kill you.
With this?
Nice.
That would be easy.
However, your wife...
Do you know how she died?
I told you that, right?
Shut up.
She was fighting for her life.
I am satisfied with you, Boran.
Do not destroy yourself, please.
This is not the last time.
We must meet at the place of gathering.
Her vessels were torn.
Shut up, shut up.
But don't worry, mad Boran.
I will also send you
where your wife is.
Come on, come on, do your work, mad Boran.
Did you think that would be easy?
Demon.
What have I told you?
I said I won't die before I
make you live the pain...
you made Gonja live through twice as much.
I...
No, no.
No.
You will be out of breath first.
No!
Your throat will burn with a flame.
Your vessels will burn one by one as if
they were in the middle of a fire.
Your body will burn from the
inside and turn to ashes.
No!
For my Gonca!
Sleep well, my Gonca.
Sleep well.
Why were you so surprised
when you saw me?
You heard that Osman attacked me
on the Nicaea Road, right?
Geyhatu, I am grateful to you.
I survived thanks to your soldiers.
Speak clearly, Nikola.
The life of a person who speaks
clearly is long.
When Osman heard that I united with you...
he tried to harm me.
Although he had dozens of
reasons to kill me.
Whatever.
Your soldiers started attacking
when they saw Osman.
And I continued on my way, Geyhatu.
What were you doing in Iznik?
I talked about the idea of ​​becoming a
state, which you proposed to me...
with Emperor Andronikos.
What?
What did you do?
Master, hide the Greek fire.
I will blow them up
to the side of Geyhatu.
My Bey, people live to die.
Inshallah I will also see those conquests.
Master Davud, you are a Master.
You will be by my side.
We'll shoot those
castles with your shells.
However...
do you know who will throw them?
You should meet him.
Shepherd brother.
You can call me Akça, Master
Davud.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
Boran.
Your face is shining, my brother.
My Bey, I sent that demon to hell.
I killed Julia, my Bey.
Today is my feast.
From now on, the breath I breathe
won't hurt me, my Bey.
From now on...
my Bey...
Brother, this is the end of all cruels.
Thank Allah I saw you like that.
Amin, my Bey.
My Bey.
Güngüz Bey is going to see Geyhatu.
Let's go and see Gündüz Bey.
Let's see if he is still with the cruels.
Or...
Or is there a little mercy in his heart?
If he is still one of the cruels, I'm
sorry for him.
Let's go.
Why are you so nervous, Vizier Alemşah?
I'm still with you.
I should have taken the emperor's
approval, that's just the matter.
Why?
So that the emperor won't send an army to
attack me...
when you leave these lands, Geyhatu.
You went to see the emperor and told
him that you will establish a state...
and you got out
safely, didn't you, Nikola?
Yes.
This is exactly what happened.
The emperor is very afraid of Geyhatu.
If Geyhatu says that Nikola
will be the emperor.
The Emperor Andronikos will not
think for a moment...
and he will leave his throne and his
crown and give me Constantinople.
He told me, "Don't piss them off and do
whatever they want."
If there's something bad in this, I'll rip
your heart out and feed it to the dogs.
No trick, Geyhatu.
Emperor Andronikos.
He wants us to put the Turks among
us and crush them like flies.
Roma is with you, great Geyhatu.
Help Geyhatu to stop the Turks.
The Emperor.
Good.
Go now, Gündüz will come.
He shouldn't see you.
Whatever you want.
Stupid Nikola.
I don't know what he's up to.
But I'll take Inegol from him.
Even if there was a trick, he wouldn't
live enough to complete it.
We will enter his castle amicably.
And we'll take it out from under him.
Nikola hasn't learned to
sit on his castle.
When the Greek fire comes, and then no
one will be able to stand in our way.
Speak.
The soldiers sent by Argun Khan...
and the unit was destroyed.
The Greek fire...
is unavailable.
You didn't even tell me about the route.
How and who got the news, Geyhatu?
Osman.
- Gündüz Bey.
- Osman Bey.
Come here.
Come here, Gündüz Bey.
I don't want the blood of my brothers
and Alps to be shed.
You want to hurt Turks with the cruels...
with the support of the Alps.
They are not to blame.
You...
were deceived by the Vizier and Geyhatu
and you deceive them.
All my life...
I witnessed what your sword
did to the cruel people.
Since you are one of the cruels now...
then...
meet my sword of my justice.
Come on, Gündüz Bey.
Since you consider me as an enemy...
Then I won't back down, brother.
After all the betrayals you've done...
after all the cruelty,do you still call
me my brother?
Wha brother?
From now on, I'm not your brother.
I don't give up on my brother.
Because of the betrayals you've made...
your blood is halal.
You betrayed your ancestral inheritance.
You are a brother who left his
brother among traitors.
You are a Bey who has turned
his back on his state.
You will leave this world now...
without a brother...
nor customs...
nor a homeland.
Come here.
Come on.
Come on, brother.
After all the betrayals...
After all the cruelty...
you will be a brother killer.
Come on.
Your instinct is like the instinct of Cain.
I didn't want to be Cain...
nor to be a traitor.
The sword of justice...
can...
take my soul.
Alps!
You should know...
what I did was...
not because of my greed, nor because
of my love for the position.
Remember me as someone who veered
out of his way...
thinking about the safety of the Kayı.
The time has come, my brother.
Our ways are separated.
You are on the right path...
and I am the one who blinded his eyes by
the curtain of omission.
I made a mistake.
I was oblivious.
From now on, my blood is halal
for you, my brother.
Come on, brother
Come on.
Our ways were the same.
However, you couldn't walk.
Our goal was the same.
You didn't keep it.
I was behind you like a mountain.
However, you didn't stand upright.
The cost is now known.
Who does not stand by his words...
ends up like this.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com